Personal details

Name: Joey ter Meulen Location: Barcelona, Spain Phone: 0043 679 308 440

E-mail: joeytermeulen@gmail.com

Date of birth: 16-02-1989

Nationality: Dutch

Overview

Hello! I am Joey, a 31-year-old frontend web developer from Amsterdam, the Netherlands. In 2017 I discovered coding and after extensive home studies, I officially joined the development industry at the start of 2018. I have since been professionally developing websites, focusing on React.js, Node.js and GraphQI.

With 3 years of working experience, React.js is my main strength - but in my spare time, Unity and C# take over. Coding games is just as fun!

I recently moved to Barcelona and I'm looking for a fresh new challenge at a company that champions their team spirit as much as their product. I enjoy working with other crafts, collaborating daily with UI/UX, QA and backend developers. I'm always open to feedback and new ideas and can handle stress very well. I am organised, make quick decisions and I can lead a group when I need to.

Job experience

April 2018 -December 2020 **LeoVegas** Luntmakargatan 18, 111 37 Stockholm, Sweden

Occupation: Frontend WebDeveloper (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

Job description: LeoVegas is an online casino provider. My daily job includes developing

new features, especially to enhance the game experience for players. I work with React.js, Node.js and GraphQl on a daily basis. Other responsibilities include writing tests for the features we develop, maintain and bug-fix any feature previously released, and close collaboration between designers and

BackEnd developers.

September 2016 -January 2018

Swagg Elektravägen 5, 126 30 Hägersten, Sweden

Occupation: Textile printer (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

Job description: Manually and mechanically printing of textile, starting with

digitally designing and preparing the printing process, all the way to the

printing itself.

July 2015 -July 2016 **Expeditors** Ganderweg 1, 1118 LH, Schiphol, Netherlands

Occupation: Warehouse employee (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

Job description: Breaking down freight from plates by hand and with a

forklift, unloading and loading trucks with pallets and packages. Scanning

and storing the freight in the warehouse.

January 2009 -July 2015 **Refero** Kollenbergweg 78B, 1101 AV, Amsterdam, Netherlands

Occupation: Textile printer, manager (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

Job description: Manually and mechanically printing of textile, starting with

digitally designing and preparing the printing process, all the way to the printing itself. I was also responsible for planning and managing the

workfloor.

January 2008 -January 209 **Schiphol Airport** employment agency Content, Amsterdam, Netherlands

Occupation: Flight Ramp agent (36 hours a week)

Job description: Loading and unloading cargo and baggage on and off

airplanes.

Through internal courses, my responsibilities extended to docking

incoming airplanes.

Skills

Javascript	
React.js	••••••
HTML5	••••••
CSS	••••••
Redux	•••••••
Node.js	••••••
Express	••••••000
C# / Unity	●●●●○○○○
Python	●●●●●○○○○

Education and Courses

2020	CodeWithMosh - <u>Java Mastery Series</u>
2020	Udemy - Node.JS Advanced Course
2019	Udemy - Unity 2D Game Dev Course
2019	Udemy - <u>Unreal Engine Game Dev Course</u>
2018	Udemy - ECMAScript 6 Course

2018 Udemy - React Complete Guide

2017 Udemy - <u>Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp</u>

2017 **Udemy - Web Developer Bootcamp**

2017 LearnCodeTheHardWay - Book on the principles of coding in Python

2007-2008 InHolland - HBO Commercial Economics 2001-2007 Calandlyceum Amsterdam - HAVO Graduated